<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<spetml:page templateName="mainPage" title="Solar Products" xmlns:spetml="http://www.spetnik.com/2013/spetml">

	<sl:description xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix">
		Solar panels, solar mass, and solar wafers are just some of the products we offer
	</sl:description>

	<sl:topWidget name="banner" xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix" />

	<sl:mainFrame xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix">
		<h3>Large range of<br/><span class="line2">Solar Products</span></h3>
		<p>
			Here at <a href="/">Solar Logistix</a>, we go beyond power. Our exclusive
			solar products allow you to experience the Sun here on Earth.
		</p>

		<h4>PURESOLAR&#8482; Panels</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="Solar Panels" src="/files/images/imgpanels.jpg" />
			PURESOLAR&#8482; Panels are our patented, environmentally-friendly solar
			grid panels. Made from the talons of spotted owls, the panel frames are
			rigid and can survive even the closest contact with the sun.<br /><br />
			We believe that things from space should be installed by people from space.
			Therefore every <a href="/">Solar Logistix</a> installation is performed
			by an actual NASA astronaut.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> to get started with your
			own solar panels today.
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />

		<h4>Solar Mass</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="Solar Mass" src="/files/images/imgsolarmass.jpg" />
			Solar mass is no longer just for physicists and astronomers. Now you can
			receive your own glob of smoldering solar mass just for yourself. Hotter than
			lava, we mine our solar mass up close from the base of coronal mass ejections.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> to find out how you can
			purchase solar mass for your home or business.
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />

		<h4>Solar Wafers</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="Solar Wafers" src="/files/images/imgwafer.jpg" />
			Need a hot meal? Nothing is hotter than our solar wafers. These wafers are
			made from fused hydrogen taken from the sun's core, sliced thin, and layered
			with a rich cream filling. Lighter than air, these wafers will have you floating
			on a ray of sunshine.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> for pricing and more information.
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />
	</sl:mainFrame>
</spetml:page>
