<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<spetml:page templateName="mainPage" title="Our Services" xmlns:spetml="http://www.spetnik.com/2013/spetml">

	<sl:description xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix">
		High-bandwidth clean power and other solar solutions
	</sl:description>

	<sl:topWidget name="banner" xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix" />

	<sl:mainFrame xmlns:sl="http://example.com/solarlogistix">
		<h3>Clean Power and Other<br/><span class="line2">Solar Services</span></h3>
		<p>
			Whatever it is that your business needs on the web, we have a solution for you.
		</p>

		<h4>Solar Power Collection</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="Solar Panels" src="/files/images/imgprobe.jpg" />
			<a href="/">Solar Logistix</a> is the only company that actually mines
			power directly from the surface of the sun. This means raw power, with
			no atmospheric scattering or cooling, delivered directly to your solar
			panels. No more waiting for the sun to come out. With <a href="/">Solar Logistix</a>,
			the sun is always shining.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> to get a quote on solar powering
			your home or business.
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />

		<h4>Alternative Light</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="No more lightbulbs" src="/files/images/imglightbulb.jpg" />
			Now you can go ahead and break every light bulb in your home or business.
			When you subscribe to <a href="/">Solar Logistix</a>'s Alternative light&#8482;
			service, you will receive your light directly through your solar panels -
			straight from the sun. Live in an area that has clouds? Our Rainy Day Add-on
			Package will give you light even at the darkest of times.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> to get started now!
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />

		<h4>Solar Transport</h4>
		<p class="indent">
			<img class="left" alt="Solar transport" src="/files/images/imgrocket.jpg" />
			<a href="/">Solar Logistix</a> has high-tech spacecraft visiting the Sun
			frequently. Not only do we retrieve power from the sun, but we also refuel
			it when it is running low (e.g. in the winter). Our spacecraft carry thousands
			of gallons of molten lava from active volcanoes and, after refining it in space-borne
			centrifuges, deliver it directly to loading docks on the solar surface.
			<br /><br/>
			Want to visit the Sun? Our space tourism division can help you arrange a
			private trip for your family or co-workers.
			<br /><br/>
			<a href="/company-contact/quote">Click here</a> for pricing and more information.
		</p>
		<div class="clear" />
	</sl:mainFrame>
</spetml:page>